ABHISHEK PATNAIK

Summary

Marketing and Alliance Manager with experience in brand management, corporate alliances and promotion. Strength in working with diverse groups to achieve company objectives. My recent experience involved as an Alliance manager for Hospitality & Lifestyle industry. Efficient in making a significant contribution to the company with my experience in business strategies, operations, marketing, and sales.

Employment

Things2Do Manager Business Alliances

Bengaluru July 2021 to Jan. 2023

- Acquiring and engaging the right set of Luxury, F&B, Travel, Adventure partners in Bengaluru
- Contact and secure new merchants/vendors through a relationship-based approach.
- Understand & Co-create experiences with the merchant partner
- Demonstrating the content commerce features and benefits of our products.
- Building contacts across Luxury, FnB, Wellness, Hotels, Staycation, Activities & Unique Experiences, Transactional/ E-com websites
- Collaborate and handle team for execution of events and promotions.

OYO Hotels & Homes Pvt Ltd Demand Manager | Key Accounts Manager

Bengaluru , Karnataka, India June 2019 to July 2021

- Identify/Onboard/Develop Channel partners
- Periodic market research for finding different avenues for data mining and generating prospects
- Understand clients requirements and custom make the product portfolio accordingly
- Efficient Planning and Executing market-site visits within the assigned region.
- Maintain and review monthly Sales Tracker of accounts and targets
- Collection of accounts receivable/outstanding amount from clients/accounts
- Drive Off Line Sales through cold calling and meeting potential clients/corporates to sell OYO

 Portfolio
- Responsible for team management and end-to-end sales process.
- Qualifying clients and closing deals with retaining/acquiring new accounts/clients
- Internal stakeholder management

Ivaan Health Services Pvt Ltd - IHS Senior Marketing and Sales Executive

Hyderabad, Telengana , India May 2016 to June 2019

- Comprehensive Marketing Support for the planning of Events Promotions & Collaterals
- Creating promotional Sales Schemes through Digital Marketing
- Promotional events near Major Hospitals for Lead generation and Conversion.
- Online Video Consultation facilitation between Doctor (India) and Patient (Abroad)
- Handling Customer Inquiries from Website and Social Networks and providing them guidance
- Alliances and Tie-ups with potential Medical and Tourism organisations
- Company Corporate Website and Social Network management.
- Customer Service on the ground for International and Domestic patients in Hospitals
- Working with Hospital Administration & other teams for proper flow of information and Service.
- Customer Follow-up and referral management
- Handled on ground Sales team, Alliances & Marketing team.

Flipkart India Private Limited Customer Support Executive | Inside Sales | Large appliances category

Bengaluru, Karnataka Apr. 2014 to Apr. 2016

Handling both Pre-Sales and Post Sales Customer queries

Incident Management and Follow up

Collaborating with multiple teams and vendors to provide a solution to the customer

Customer Account Update and Validation

Large category products pre-sales and post-sales assistance

Key Work

Hospital Alliances & Promotion in Dhaka, Bangladesh

- Alliances Onboarding and Sales, Onboarding Channel Partners, Identifying new partners and creating new alliances (Hospital and Tourism), Generating Leads & training
- INR 30 Lakh Revenue generated through lead generations and service

On boarded CAT-A Corporates | OYO Hotels & Homes

- On-boarded CAT-A corporate accounts which generate minimum revenue of 2-4 Lac/Per month.
- Created a sale RR (Room revenue) estimated value of 2 Lac/Per month.

Partner Alliances for F&B | Nightlife | Activities & Experiences | Things2do

- Onboarded 20 Five Star category Hotels & Luxury partners for curating experiences in Bengaluru.
- Onboarded nightlife places and experience places that are popular in Bengaluru.
- Handled events and parties organised by partners and handled ticket sales through channels.
- Created Merchant and Vendor network for experience curation in Bengaluru city

Contact

■ abhishekpattnayak@outlook.com

P-7406785421 | W 8309558141

♥ Bengaluru, Karnataka, India in abhishek-p-6b7401b0

Education

Berhampur University

Master's Degree Mass Communication 2013

Berhampur University

Bachelor's Degree Commerce 2011

Khallikote University, Berhampur

Senior Secondary Commerce 2008

Matrusri Anglo Vedic School

Schooling Secondary Education 2006

Skills

SALES & MARKETING

B2B & B2C

Key Accounts Management

Channel Partner

Enterprise Sales

Corporate Sales

Business Development

Digital Marketing

OPERATIONS AND MANAGEMENT

Corporate tie up

Channel Partner

Administration

Medical Tourism

Medical Sales & Service

BUSINESS STRATEGY, PROJECT MANAGEMENT

Targeted Implementation

Project Development & Implementation

Social Media Management

E-COMMERCE OPERATION AND MANAGEMENT

Pre & Post Sales

Order Management

Escalations

Vendor management

CLIENT/CUSTOMER MANAGEMENT

Key Accounts

SPOC

Customer Support

Corporate Account Management

HOSPITALITY

Hospital Industry | Hotel Industry | Tourism Industry

Partner Alliances

Vendor Management